AYOBAMI — ADEOLU

■ PRODUCT DESIGNER

+2347087980073 | SOJIADEOLU1@GMAIL.COM

DRIBBBLE.COM/EMMACREATIVE | AYOADEOLU.COM

ABOUT

Product designer with 3+ years experience working as visual designer, branding expert and UI/UX Designer. I've had the privilege of working on creative teams for companies and start ups on freelance, remote and full time basis and I have carried out several projects on small and large scales.

I am a team player, I can leverage on proven achievements, working knowledge of design softwares and methodology to deliver professionally as expected.

SKILLS

| Figma | Adobe XD | Keynote |
|-------------------|----------|----------|
| | | |
| Adobe Illustrator | Framer | Sketch |
| | | |
| Photoshop | Invision | HTML/CSS |
| | | |

TRAINING/COURSES

STUTERN GRADUATE ACCELERATOR

 ${\tt COMPLETED}$

EDUCATION

2013 - 2018

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

OBAFEMI AWOLOWO UNIVERSITY

HOBBIES

| Photography | Traveling | Movies |
|-------------|-----------|------------|
| | | |
| Music | Metaverse | Meditation |

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan. 2021 - Present

ARCHIRALD LONDON

PRODUCT DESIGNER

- Work with engineering and product stakeholders to design, prototype and validate new and existing products
- Uphold standard design practices by creating and maintaining design systems and clearly communicating the rationale behind UX designs
- Executed user research and visual design for the e-commerce web and mobile app (iOS and Android).

Jun. 2019 - Dec. 2020

NATURES OWN WONDER

PRODUCT DESIGNER

- Wireframed user flows, user stories and user interfaces of several end-to-end mobile and web apps.
- Designed 2 fin-tech applications, 3 e-commerce marketplaces, 1 learning management systems, and over 12 corporate websites and landing pages.

Mar. 2019 - May 2019

SCELLOO - INTERSHIP

UI/UX DESIGNER

- Arranged the end-to-end user research and user interface design of 3 flagship enterprise products as well as the company's 1st ever design system.
- Worked effectively with the design team towards the execution of user research, user testing and creation of wireframes, visual design, flows and prototypes for web and mobile apps.

Jan. 2019 - June 2020

VORTEX247

DIGITAL DESIGNER

- Created websites using WordPress CMS and handled copywriting for landing pages, email newsletters, online advertisements, blog posts and search engine optimization.
- Reduced the company's marketing budget by 18% by creating and impementing growth hack strategies.